Women's Bookstore collection
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Subject files, 1937 - 1990; F-111-7; 1.94 m of textual records; Predominant dates: 1965-1985.
  - General, 1937 - 1990; F-111-7-1; 1.37 m of textual records
    - Media, 1970 - 1976; F-111-7-1-0-46 (Archival box - standard 111-12)
    - Men's Liberation, 1969 - 1974; F-111-7-1-0-47 (Archival box - standard 111-12)
    - Native Women, 1975 - 1978; F-111-7-1-0-48 (Archival box - standard 111-12)
    - Pedestal correspondence, 1970 - 1974; F-111-7-1-0-49 (Archival box - standard 111-12)
      The Pedestal; Textual records
    - Politics, 1969 - 1981; F-111-7-1-0-50 (Archival box - standard 111-12)
    - Pornography, 1982 - 1983; F-111-7-1-0-51 (Archival box - standard 111-12)
    - Prostitution, F-111-7-1-0-52 (Archival box - standard 111-12)
    - Psychology of Women, 1970 - 1981; F-111-7-1-0-53 (Archival box - standard 111-12)
    - Race, 1968 - 1975; F-111-7-1-0-54 (Archival box - standard 111-13)
    - Rape, 1971 - 1980; F-111-7-1-0-55 (Archival box - standard 111-13)
    - Religion, 1971 - 1982; F-111-7-1-0-56 (Archival box - standard 111-13)
    - Sex Role Stereotypes 1/2, 1969 - 1975; F-111-7-1-0-57 (Archival box - standard 111-13)
    - Sex Role Stereotypes 2/2, 1969 - 1975; F-111-7-1-0-58 (Archival box - standard 111-13)
    - Sex Role Stereotypes - Teacher's Kit, 1972 - 1974; F-111-7-1-0-59 (Archival box - standard 111-13)
    - Socialism 1/2, 1969 - 1981; F-111-7-1-0-60 (Archival box - standard 111-13)
    - Socialism 2/2, 1969 - 1981; F-111-7-1-0-61 (Archival box - standard 111-14)
    - Sports and Leisure, 1972 - 1982; F-111-7-1-0-62 (Archival box - standard 111-14)
    - Third World, 1968 - 1982; F-111-7-1-0-63 (Archival box - standard 111-14)
    - Unions, 1971 - 1980; F-111-7-1-0-64 (Archival box - standard 111-14)
    - Vancouver Public Library, F-111-7-1-0-65 (Archival box - standard 111-14)
      Vancouver Public Library; Textual records
    - War and Military, F-111-7-1-0-66 (Archival box - standard 111-14)
    - Welfare, 1969 - 1978; F-111-7-1-0-67 (Archival box - standard 111-14)
    - Women's Day, 1967 - 1979; F-111-7-1-0-68 (Archival box - standard 111-14)
    - Women's Movement - ephemera, 1975 - 1981; F-111-7-1-0-69 (Archival box - standard 111-14)
    - Women's Movement - Australia/New Zealand, 1975 - 1982; F-111-7-1-0-70 (Archival box - standard 111-14)
    - Women's Movement - Quebec, 1970 - 1981; F-111-7-1-0-71 (Archival box - standard 111-14)
    - Women's Movement - U.S. 1/2, 1969 - 1979; F-111-7-1-0-72 (Archival box - standard 111-15)
    - Women's Movement - U.S. 2/2, 1969 - 1979; F-111-7-1-0-73 (Archival box - standard 111-15)
    - Women's Movement - U.S. newspapers, 1970 - 1982; F-111-7-1-0-74 (Archival box - standard 111-15)
    - Women's Studies 1/2, 1970 - 1984; F-111-7-1-0-75 (Archival box - standard 111-15)
    - Women's Studies 2/2, 1970 - 1984; F-111-7-1-0-76 (Archival box - standard 111-15)
    - Women's Studies - SFU, 1972 - 1977; F-111-7-1-0-77 (Archival box - standard 111-16)
    - Women's Studies - UBC, 1969 - 1975; F-111-7-1-0-78 (Archival box - standard 111-16)
    - Work 1/2, 1968 - 1981; F-111-7-1-0-79 (Archival box - standard 111-16)
    - Work 2/2, 1968 - 1981; F-111-7-1-0-80 (Archival box - standard 111-16)
    - Work - Housework, 1967 - 1981; F-111-7-1-0-81 (Archival box - standard 111-16)
    - Work - Papers and periodicals, 1968 - 1981; F-111-7-1-0-82 (Archival box - standard 111-16)
    - Work - Papers and presentations, 1970 - 1981; F-111-7-1-0-83 (Archival box - standard 111-16)
    - Posters, vol. 1, 1975 - 1990; F-111-7-1-0-84
    - Posters, vol. 2, 1975 - 1990; F-111-7-1-0-85
    - Posters, vol. 3, 1975 - 1990; F-111-7-1-0-86
    - Posters, vol. 4, 1975 - 1990; F-111-7-1-0-87
    - Posters, vol. 5, 1975 - 1990; F-111-7-1-0-88
    - Posters, vol. 6, 1975 - 1990; F-111-7-1-0-89
    - Posters, vol. 7, 1975 - 1990; F-111-7-1-0-90
    - Posters, vol. 8, 1975 - 1990; F-111-7-1-0-91
  - Feminist organizations and movements, 1968 - 1985; F-111-7-2; 50 cm of textual records
    Sub-series consists of reference files relating feminist organizations. For list of organizations, see Access Points.
    - B.C. Association of Midwives, 1980 - 1981; F-111-7-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 111-17)
      British Columbia Association of Midwives; Textual records
    - B.C. Task Force on Immigrant Women, 1982; F-111-7-2-0-2 (Archival box - standard 111-17)
      British Columbia Task Force on Immigrant Women; Textual records
    - B.C. Women's Abortion Law-repeal Coalition, 1971 - 1973; F-111-7-2-0-3 (Archival box - standard 111-17)
      British Columbia Women's Abortion Law Repeal Coalition; Textual records
    - Canadian Association for Repeal of the Abortion Law (CARAL), 1973 - 1977; F-111-7-2-0-4 (Archival box - standard 111-17)
      Canadian Abortion Rights Action League; Textual records
    - Childcare Occupation Forces, 1973; F-111-7-2-0-5 (Archival box - standard 111-17)
      Childcare Occupation Forces; Textual records
    - Concerned Aboriginal Women - Occupation of DIAND, 1978 - 1981; F-111-7-2-0-6 (Archival box - standard 111-17)
      File consists of a press release, a set of telexes supporting the women (ca 50 pages), text of a speech by Flora MaDonald MP, and a wide-distribution letter from the Concerned Aboriginal Women addressed "To All Support Groups."
      Department of Indian Affairs and Northern Development; MacDonald, Flora; Concerned Aboriginal Women; Textual records
    - Concerned Citizens for Choice on Abortion, 1980 - 1981; F-111-7-2-0-7 (Archival box - standard 111-17)
      Concerned Citizens for Choice on Abortion; Textual records
    - Day Care Organizing Committee (package) - Toronto, 1970 - 1971; F-111-7-2-0-8 (Archival box - standard 111-17)
      Day Care Organizing Committee (Toronto); Textual records
    - Feminist News Service, 1974 - 1976; F-111-7-2-0-9 (Archival box - standard 111-17)
      Feminist News Service; Textual records
    - Greater Vancouver Federated Anti-Poverty Groups, 1974 - 1976; F-111-7-2-0-10 (Archival box - standard 111-17)
      Greater Vancouver Federated Anti-Poverty Groups; Textual records
    - International Feminist League of Hong Kong, 1973; F-111-7-2-0-11 (Archival box - standard 111-17)
      International Feminist League of Hong Kong; Textual records
    - Manitoba Abortion Action Coalition, 1971; F-111-7-2-0-12 (Archival box - standard 111-17)
      Manitoba Abortion Action Coalition; Textual records
    - National Anti-Poverty Organization, 1972 - 1975; F-111-7-2-0-13 (Archival box - standard 111-17)
      National Anti-Poverty Organization; Textual records
    - Search Youth Group - correspondence received, 1978 - 1981; F-111-7-2-0-14 (Archival box - standard 111-17)
      Search Youth Group; Textual records
    - Service, Office, and Retail Workers' Union of Canada (SORWUC), 1975 - 1980; F-111-7-2-0-15 (Archival box - standard 111-17)
      Service, Office, and Retail Workers Union of Canada; Textual records
    - Society for the Happiness of Our Offspring, 1971; F-111-7-2-0-16 (Archival box - standard 111-18)
      Society for the Happiness of Our Offspring; Textual records
    - Solidarity Coalition, 1983 - 1985; F-111-7-2-0-17 (Archival box - standard 111-18)
      Solidarity Coalition; Textual records
    - Status of Women, 1973 - 1976; F-111-7-2-0-18 (Archival box - standard 111-18)
      Status of Women Council; Textual records
    - Status of Women, 1973 - 1981; F-111-7-2-0-19 (Archival box - standard 111-18)
    - Status of Women - Manitoba Action Committee on the Status of Women, 1980; F-111-7-2-0-20 (Archival box - standard 111-18)
    - Status of Women - National Action Committee on the Status of Women, 1973 - 1981; F-111-7-2-0-21 (Archival box - standard 111-18)
    - Status of Women - Royal Commission for the Status of Women, 1968 - 1971; F-111-7-2-0-22 (Archival box - standard 111-18)
    - Status of Women - Sarnia-Lambton, 1976; F-111-7-2-0-23 (Archival box - standard 111-18)
    - Status of Women - Vancouver Status of Women, 1972 - 1981; F-111-7-2-0-24 (Archival box - standard 111-18)
    - Status of Women - Victoria, 1974 - 1976; F-111-7-2-0-25 (Archival box - standard 111-18)
    - Toronto Women's Bookstore, 1974; F-111-7-2-0-26 (Archival box - standard 111-18)
      Toronto Women's Bookstore; Textual records
    - Vancouver Opportunities Program and "Help Yourself", 1969 - 1975; F-111-7-2-0-27 (Archival box - standard 111-19)
    - Vancouver Rape Relief, 1980 - 1982; F-111-7-2-0-28 (Archival box - standard 111-19)
      Vancouver Rape Relief; Textual records
    - Vancouver Resources Board, 1974; F-111-7-2-0-29 (Archival box - standard 111-19)
      Vancouver Resources Board; Textual records
    - Arts - Vancouver Women in Focus Society, 1980; F-111-7-2-0-30 (Archival box - standard 111-19)
      Vancouver Women in Focus Society; Textual records
    - Vancouver Women's Health Collective, 1974 - 1980; F-111-7-2-0-31 (Archival box - standard 111-19)
      Vancouver Women's Health Collective; Textual records
    - Vancouver Women's Interart Society, 1978 - 1980; F-111-7-2-0-32 (Archival box - standard 111-19)
      Vancouver Women's Interart Society; Textual records
    - Western Conference of Opportunities for Women, 1973 - 1974; F-111-7-2-0-33 (Archival box - standard 111-19)
      Western Conference of Opportunities for Women; Textual records
    - Women Against the Budget, 1983 - 1985; F-111-7-2-0-34 (Archival box - standard 111-19)
      Women Against the Budget; Textual records
    - Women in Trades, 1980 - 1983; F-111-7-2-0-35 (Archival box - standard 111-19)
      Vancouver Women in Trades; Textual records
    - Women Rally for Action, 1976; F-111-7-2-0-36 (Archival box - standard 111-19)
      Women Rally for Action; Textual records
    - Women's Caucus of the New University Conference, 1968 - 1969; F-111-7-2-0-37 (Archival box - standard 111-19)
    - Women's Liberation - Ontario, 1969 - 1971; F-111-7-2-0-38 (Archival box - standard 111-19)
    - Women's Liberation - Organization / Strategy 1/2, 1968 - 1972; F-111-7-2-0-39 (Archival box - standard 111-19)
    - Women's Liberation - Organization / Strategy 2/2, 1968 - 1972; F-111-7-2-0-40 (Archival box - standard 111-20)
    - Women's Liberation - Newsletter / Journals 1/2, 1969 - 1980; F-111-7-2-0-41 (Archival box - standard 111-20)
    - Women's Liberation - Newsletter / Journals 2/2, 1969 - 1980; F-111-7-2-0-42 (Archival box - standard 111-20)
    - Women's Liberation - Sweden, 1971; F-111-7-2-0-43 (Archival box - standard 111-20)
    - Women's Research Centre, 1977 - 1978; F-111-7-2-0-44 (Archival box - standard 111-20)
      Women's Research Centre; Textual records
    - Working Women's Association, 1971 - 1973; F-111-7-2-0-45 (Archival box - standard 111-20)
      Working Women's Association; Textual records
    - Younger Lesbian Association, 1980; F-111-7-2-0-46 (Archival box - standard 111-20)
      Younger Lesbian Association; Textual records
    - YWCA - Toronto, 1973 - 1985; F-111-7-2-0-47 (Archival box - standard 111-20)
      YWCA (Toronto); Textual records
    - YWCA - Vancouver, 1973 - 1981; F-111-7-2-0-48 (Archival box - standard 111-20)
      YWCA (Vancouver); Textual records
    - YWCA - Winnipeg "Herself", 1975 - 1976; F-111-7-2-0-49 (Archival box - standard 111-20)
      YWCA (Winnipeg); Textual records
- Publications, 1969 - 1997; F-111-8; 2.3 m of textual records 212 newspapers
  Series consists of a collection of feminist newspapers, journals, and newsletters documenting the women's movement in North America. Includes publications from British Columbia and the rest of Canada, the United States, and some examples from Australia, and England. Includes fairly extensive runs of issues of Kinesis (file 39, 1974-1987), Majority Report (file 47, 1973-1977), Off Our Backs (file 63, 1970-1980), and The Other Woman (file 67, 1972-1976).
  An item list is available for newspapers in this series.
  - Akwesasne Notes, 1970 - 1971; F-111-8-0-0-1 (Urc tote box 111-21)
  - The Arrow, 1974 - 1975; F-111-8-0-0-2 (Urc tote box 111-21)
  - AUCE: Anchor, 1979 - 1985; F-111-8-0-0-3 (Urc tote box 111-21)
    Association of University and College Employees, Local 2; Textual records
  - Big Mama Rag, 1975 - 1980; F-111-8-0-0-4 (Urc tote box 111-21)
  - Blackout, 1981 - 1983; F-111-8-0-0-5 (Urc tote box 111-21)
  - Body Politic, 1979 - 1981; F-111-8-0-0-6 (Urc tote box 111-21)
  - Branching Out, 1973 - 1980; F-111-8-0-0-7 (Urc tote box 111-21)
  - Bread and Roses, 1970 - 1976; F-111-8-0-0-8 (Urc tote box 111-21)
  - Broadside, 1979 - 1983; F-111-8-0-0-9 (Urc tote box 111-21)
  - Calgary Women's Newspaper, 1980 - 1981; F-111-8-0-0-10 (Urc tote box 111-21)
  - Canadian Newsletter of Research on Women, 1972 - 1975; F-111-8-0-0-11 (Urc tote box 111-21)
  - Canadian Women and Religion Newsletter, 1975; F-111-8-0-0-12 (Urc tote box 111-21)
  - Catalist / Fed-Up Newsletter, 1975 - 1980; F-111-8-0-0-13 (Urc tote box 111-21)
  - Change, 1972 - 1973; F-111-8-0-0-14 (Urc tote box 111-21)
  - City Farmer, 1978 - 1981; F-111-8-0-0-15 (Urc tote box 111-21)
  - Communiqu'elles, 1981 - 1982; F-111-8-0-0-16 (Urc tote box 111-21)
  - Concerning Women and You, 1978 - 1979; F-111-8-0-0-17 (Urc tote box 111-21)
  - Crosscurrents, 1975 - 1976; F-111-8-0-0-18 (Urc tote box 111-21)
  - C.A.R.D.W.O. Newsletter, 1982; F-111-8-0-0-19 (Urc tote box 111-21)
  - England - Miscellaneous, 1970 - 1972; F-111-8-0-0-20 (Urc tote box 111-21)
  - Entrelles, 1980; F-111-8-0-0-21 (Urc tote box 111-21)
  - Equal Times, [ca 1970] - [ca 1979]; F-111-8-0-0-22 (Urc tote box 111-22)
  - Everywoman, 1970 - 1971; F-111-8-0-0-23 (Urc tote box 111-22)
  - The Feminist, 1974 - 1975; F-111-8-0-0-24 (Urc tote box 111-22)
  - Feminist Bookstore News, 1980 - 1997; F-111-8-0-0-25 (Urc tote box 111-27)
  - Feminist Communication Collective, 1974 - 1975; F-111-8-0-0-26 (Urc tote box 111-22)
  - The Feminist Voice, 1972; F-111-8-0-0-27 (Urc tote box 111-22)
  - Focus, 1980 - 1981; F-111-8-0-0-28 (Urc tote box 111-22)
  - The Freedom Socialist, 1979; F-111-8-0-0-29 (Urc tote box 111-22)
  - Gay Tide, 1973 - 1980; F-111-8-0-0-30 (Urc tote box 111-22)
  - Grapevine, 1973 - 1980; F-111-8-0-0-31 (Urc tote box 111-22)
  - guerilla, [ca 1970] - [ca 1979]; F-111-8-0-0-32 (Urc tote box 111-22)
  - HealthRight, 1974 - 1978; F-111-8-0-0-33 (Urc tote box 111-22)
  - Healthsharing, 1979 - 1986; F-111-8-0-0-34 (Urc tote box 111-22)
  - Hogtown Press, Toronto, [ca 1970] - [ca 1979]; F-111-8-0-0-35 (Urc tote box 111-22)
  - Images, 1974 - 1976; F-111-8-0-0-36 (Urc tote box 111-22)
  - In a Nutshell, 1980 - 1981; F-111-8-0-0-37 (Urc tote box 111-22)
  - In Struggle, 1972 - 1980; F-111-8-0-0-38 (Urc tote box 111-22)
  - Kinesis, 1974 - 1986; F-111-8-0-0-39 (Newspaper box 111-28)
    Also available digitally through UBC Digital Collections at http://digitalcollections.library.ubc.ca/cdm/landingpage/collection/kinesis (last accessed April 2015).
    - Kinesis, vol. 4 no. 32, April 1974; F-111-8-0-0-39-1
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-item17.
    - Kinesis, vol. 4 no. 35, July 1974; F-111-8-0-0-39-2
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-item18.
    - Kinesis, vol. 4 no. 36, September 1974; F-111-8-0-0-39-3
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-item19.
    - Kinesis, vol. 4 no. 39, December 1974; F-111-8-0-0-39-4
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-item20.
    - Kinesis, vol. 5 no. 41, February 1975; F-111-8-0-0-39-5
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-item21.
    - Kinesis, vol. 5 no. 42, May 1975 - February 1975; F-111-8-0-0-39-6
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-item22.
    - Kinesis, vol. 5 no. 45, June 1975; F-111-8-0-0-39-7
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-item23.
    - Kinesis, vol. 5 no. 47, August 1975; F-111-8-0-0-39-8
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-item24.
    - Kinesis, vol. 5 no. 48, September 1975; F-111-8-0-0-39-9
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-item25.
    - Kinesis, vol. 5 no. 50, October 1975; F-111-8-0-0-39-10
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-item26.
    - Kinesis, vol. 5 no. 50, November 1975; F-111-8-0-0-39-11
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-item27.
    - Kinesis, vol. 5 no. 51, December 1975; F-111-8-0-0-39-12
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-item28.
    - Kinesis, vol. 5 no. 52, February 1976; F-111-8-0-0-39-13
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-item29.
    - Kinesis, vol. 5 no. 53, March 1976; F-111-8-0-0-39-14
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-item30.
    - Kinesis, vol. 5 no. 54, April 1976; F-111-8-0-0-39-15
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-item31.
    - Kinesis, vol. 5 no. 60, November 1976; F-111-8-0-0-39-16
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-item32.
    - Kinesis, vol. 6 no. 1, December 1976; F-111-8-0-0-39-17
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-item33.
    - Kinesis, vol. 6 no. 3, February 1977; F-111-8-0-0-39-18
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-item34.
    - Kinesis, vol. 6 no. 4, March 1977; F-111-8-0-0-39-19
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-item35.
    - Kinesis, vol. 6 no. 5, April 1977; F-111-8-0-0-39-20
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-item36.
    - Kinesis, vol. 6 no. 6, May 1977; F-111-8-0-0-39-21
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-item37.
    - Kinesis, vol. 6 no. 7, June 1977; F-111-8-0-0-39-22
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-item38.
    - Kinesis, vol. 6 no. 8, July 1977; F-111-8-0-0-39-23
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-item39.
    - Kinesis, vol. 6 no. 9, August 1977; F-111-8-0-0-39-24
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-item40.
    - Kinesis, vol. 6 no. 10, September 1977; F-111-8-0-0-39-25
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-item41.
    - Kinesis, vol. 6 no. 11, October 1977; F-111-8-0-0-39-26
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-item42.
    - Kinesis, vol. 6 no. 12, November 1977; F-111-8-0-0-39-27
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-item43.
    - Kinesis, vol. 7 no. 1, December 1977; F-111-8-0-0-39-28
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-item44.
    - Kinesis, vol. 7 no. 2, January 1978; F-111-8-0-0-39-29
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-item45.
    - Kinesis, vol. 7 no. 3, March 1978; F-111-8-0-0-39-30
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-item46.
    - Kinesis, vol. 7 no. 4, April 1978; F-111-8-0-0-39-31
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-item47.
    - Kinesis, vol. 7 no. 5, May 1978; F-111-8-0-0-39-32
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-item48.
    - Kinesis, vol. 7 no. 6, June 1978; F-111-8-0-0-39-33
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-item49.
    - Kinesis, vol. 7 no. 7, July 1978 - August 1978; F-111-8-0-0-39-34
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-item50.
    - Kinesis, vol. 7 no. 8, September 1978; F-111-8-0-0-39-35
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-item51.
    - Kinesis, vol. 7 no. 9, October 1978; F-111-8-0-0-39-36
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-item52.
    - Kinesis, vol. 7 no. 10, November 1978; F-111-8-0-0-39-37
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-item53.
    - Kinesis, vol. 7 no. 11, December 1978 - January 1979; F-111-8-0-0-39-38
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-item54.
    - Kinesis, vol. 7 no. 12, February 1979; F-111-8-0-0-39-39
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-item55.
    - Kinesis, vol. 8 no. 1, March 1979; F-111-8-0-0-39-40
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-item56.
    - Kinesis, April 1979 - May 1979; F-111-8-0-0-39-41
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-item57.
    - Kinesis, June 1979; F-111-8-0-0-39-42
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-item58.
    - Kinesis, July 1979; F-111-8-0-0-39-43
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-item59.
    - Kinesis, August 1979; F-111-8-0-0-39-44
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-item60.
    - Kinesis, September 1979 - October 1979; F-111-8-0-0-39-45
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-item61.
    - Kinesis, November 1979; F-111-8-0-0-39-46
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-item62.
    - Kinesis, December 1979 - January 1980; F-111-8-0-0-39-47
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-item63.
    - Kinesis, February 1980; F-111-8-0-0-39-48
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-item64.
    - Kinesis, March 1980; F-111-8-0-0-39-49
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-item65.
    - Kinesis, April 1980; F-111-8-0-0-39-50
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-item66.
    - Kinesis, May 1980; F-111-8-0-0-39-51
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-item67.
    - Kinesis, June 1980; F-111-8-0-0-39-52
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-item68.
    - Kinesis, July 1980; F-111-8-0-0-39-53
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-item69.
    - Kinesis, August 1980; F-111-8-0-0-39-54
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-item70.
    - Kinesis, September 1980 - October 1980; F-111-8-0-0-39-55
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-item71.
    - Kinesis, November 1980; F-111-8-0-0-39-56
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-item72.
    - Kinesis, December 1980 - January 1981; F-111-8-0-0-39-57
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-item73.
    - Kinesis, February 1981; F-111-8-0-0-39-58
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-item74.
    - Kinesis, March 1981; F-111-8-0-0-39-59
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-item75.
    - Kinesis, April 1981; F-111-8-0-0-39-60
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-item76.
    - Kinesis, May 1981; F-111-8-0-0-39-61
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-item77.
    - Kinesis, June 1981; F-111-8-0-0-39-62
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-item78.
    - Kinesis, July 1981 - August 1981; F-111-8-0-0-39-63
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-item79.
    - Kinesis, November 1981; F-111-8-0-0-39-64
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-item80.
    - Kinesis, February 1982; F-111-8-0-0-39-65
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-item81.
    - Kinesis, March 1982; F-111-8-0-0-39-66
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-item82.
    - Kinesis, May 1982; F-111-8-0-0-39-67
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-item83.
    - Kinesis, June 1982; F-111-8-0-0-39-68
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-item84.
    - Kinesis, July 1982 - August 1982; F-111-8-0-0-39-69
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-item85.
    - Kinesis, September 1982; F-111-8-0-0-39-70
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-item86.
    - Kinesis, October 1982; F-111-8-0-0-39-71